bangladeshdir.com 2017-05-25

# Bangladesh Directory Privacy Policy - bangladeshdir.com

**Bangladeshdir.com Privacy Policy**

You can visit Bangladeshdir.com without revealing any personal, identifiable information. Each time a visitor comes to our site, our server collects some basic technical information, including, your domain name, referral data and browser and platform type. We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, date and time etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services.

Bangladeshdir.com respects your right to the privacy of your personal information you provide us. Any personal information you provide to Bangladeshdir.com will be known only to two parties: you and bangladeshdir.com. We do not sell your personal information to others.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We use Google adsense to serve ads when you visit Bangladeshdir.com. Google uses DART cookie to serve ads to you based on your visit to Bangladeshdir.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out the use of DART cookie by visiting the [Google Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

If your website listed on our web directory, your E-Mail address, Phone/Fax numbers may be added to your website description. If you want to remove your E-mail Address, Phone/Fax numbers, Please, Contact Us.

Bangladeshdir.com contains many links to other sites on the web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

We reserve the right to change this policy policy at any time without prior notice.

If you have any further questions about our privacy policies, please [contact us](http://www.bangladeshdir.com/concat-us/).

BangladeshDir.com Privacy Policy Last updated: December 25, 2014
